{
    "id": "d6cd689317ca49dda68fbc8ffa545522",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This country is backward ..................... many aspects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc0ba9c5cb5b4d2899673f7d5a7654bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you think we can bank ………………. him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04f8fc17f9f947afb3e0290bf4a8bc51"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t believe ………………… ghosts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3c39d7b806a4d789b0c3ab6b8cf39c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Beware …………………. dogs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "away",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "be24a7f47d214a82b4e6e0c62f0a793f"
        },
        {
            "question": "During his regime, Emperor Akbar brought ……………….. many reforms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "about",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0b9fa21ee64451182c0ed8d2526b8cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is anxious ………………….. an end to these misunderstandings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "about",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb9b03e08cd44855a3030320b71341fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very bad ………………… cooking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a58dd4619d6a4f25a8b0f240c88b4745"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was blue with .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anger",
                "cold",
                "envy",
                "fear"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cd89c0c5fb864f959452ee04bf34954e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went ……………….. with envy when she saw my car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "green",
                "red",
                "blue",
                "violet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c2d8ae6ea1a64eba9d561e8f6259fa29"
        },
        {
            "question": "The principal congratulated the students ……………….. their exam results.",
            "description": "On or for is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5cac0a34479848d191a05269363630c6"
        }
    ]
}